

607 Old Highway 49, MS 39561 (601) 528-4146,

jordanparker32@gmail.com https://jordanparker32.github.io

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Motivated developer skilled at meeting customer needs with expert customer support. Stays on top of demands in fast-paced environments by effectively using slow periods. Maintains organized, clean, and safe work areas with diligent attention to important details.

# **SKILLS**

• C++

Python

JavaScript

• Git

PHF

• Website optimization

- Windows Server 2012
- Computer Repair
- Routing/switching

# **EXPERIENCE**

Web Master

November 2017 - May 2020

#### MDI | Hattiesburg, MS

- Operated as Web Master after site creation for the Mississippi Defense Initiative
- Used photo editing software and ASP.NET to market to customers by providing more effective reporting data
- Redesigned and developed a user-friendly front end, lowering initial load time over 110 seconds
- Organized social media marketing content successfully
- Supported team by providing expert administrative support, filing all records, and operating as tech support

Academic Tutor

October 2018 - May 2019

### University of Southern Mississippi | Hattiesburg, MS

- · Coordinated lesson plans, course materials, and discussion questions prior to each session
- Evaluated and documented student progress and academic challenges
- Suggested new learning resources to increase student interest and retention in the School of Computing
- Developed innovative strategies to explain C++ core concepts, adapting to diverse learning modalities

• Taught students how to study more effectively and take better notes by demonstrating consistent preparation and organization in sessions

Firearms Associate May 2017 - August 2017

### Gander Mountain | Hattiesburg, MS

- Enhanced customer satisfaction with fast, knowledgeable firearm and archery service
- Demonstrated initiative by staying busy during slow work periods, frequently handling cleaning and restocking
- Served customers by going above and beyond to offer exceptional support for all needs
- · Completed gun sales and archery repair work with little oversight

# **EDUCATION**

Information Technology Developer
University of Southern Mississippi, Hattiesburg, MS

May 2020

# **LEADERSHIP**

- ACM Elected president for ACM from 2018 to 2020.
  - o Competed in the Inter-Collegiate Programming competition for two years
  - o Freelanced computer repair and website edits to alumni's who contacted the department.
  - o Planned meetings and wrote agendas.
  - o Organized large LAN Events every month.
- IEEE Elected president for IEEE from 2019 to 2020.
  - o Spoke at the VEX State Robotics competition for two years.
  - o Project managed our robotics team.
  - o Worked to maintain the 3D Printers in the Eagle Maker Hub.